你看起来是个好孩子
Look, you seem like a nice kid,
但兄弟的未婚妻
but bros' fiancee
不能帮忙策划单身派对
cannot plan bachelor parties.
抱歉  你们俩得自食其力
Sorry. You two are on your own.
你们肯定会让我失望的
And you will disappoint me.
但记得让我失望得高兴点  好吗
But make it great, okay?
但这是一个很棒的开头
But this is a strong start.
低级生已经晋级成
The students have become...
m 20 0 l 209 0 b b b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
b
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
■
人人影视
YYeTs.com
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为更多影视更新请登陆www.YYeTs.com
原创翻译  双语字幕
中等生了
the intermediate students.
我得打个电话
I just have to make one call.
翻译：歪椅  阿蘅阿蘅  非燕  Vero
翻译：YY猫  麦田守望者  猫中之王  12CC醉芝士
你好
Hello.
罗宾  好消息
Robin, great news!
校对：卖身派对赛太公  赎身派对YY猫  总监   YY后期：孤帆    时间轴：加森  非燕
我被绑架去一个惊喜单身派对
I've been kidnapped for a surprise bachelor party
老爸老妈浪漫史第八季  第二十二集
所以我就不过去了
so I won't be there at all!
什么  巴尼  我不能单独跟你妈妈吃饭
What? Barney, I-I can't do dinner with your mom alone.
好的  我会打给她   编个借口取消掉
Okay, I'll call her, make up an excuse and cancel.